what's up everybody today we have Nick
joining the channel to talk a bit about
his journey growing leadbird Nick thanks
for coming on
thanks for having me I'm super excited
awesome well sweet so to start out
obviously I mentioned Lee bird but I
know you're a man who does many
different things in terms of software
and agency so if you're when someone
asks you what do you do how do you
summarize that down to your couple
second Pitch
so it's it's funny whenever like what I
say is like a normal friend that kind of
is going through college like ask me
what I do I just say I run a couple I
run a couple of computer software
companies because if I say SAS to them
they never know what that means or what
that is
um and so for everyone else that's
probably watching this and you know it's
actually you know intelligent with this
stuff
um I run quick lines which is a AI
personalization tool I run Libra which
is the p2b lead generation agency I'm
also a partner at inboxy which does
email warming Emmy that does email
sending and scrubby that does catch-all
email verification and golden leads that
does LinkedIn lead scraping but you know
they all kind of work together they're
all what's the word vertically
integrated with what we do at leaper but
the primary focus for the last three to
six months has been the agency just
because I enjoy it the most and that's
obviously a lot of things that I'm I'm
curious what is the first one that you
started and when was that started yeah
so the first one was Lee bird uh funny
enough so I started that almost three
years ago now and then everything kind
of came from like what we were doing
manually at leadbird so you know
obviously we had first line Riders when
we first started and so I was like all
right let's spin up quick lines
um and then like we used to manually
send to verify catch-alls using chemo
accounts and I was like oh we could
automate this let's do scrubby so
everything kind of came from the needs
at Lee bird and I think
what happened was you know running weed
bird I was like you know got the the
shiny object syndrome was like oh SAS is
the next play SAS is the next day then I
realized SAS is extremely difficult it's
not as easy and as glamorous as everyone
makes it seem to be and you know worked
on it as much as I could and still
working on it right now but then I
realized that I'm much better and built
for an agency and and you know I I think
I'm I'm very skilled at it and and so
it's it's one of those things where I
just enjoy doing it more because it's
easier to be competitive and dominate
that makes sense but that's cool and one
one question to jump into here is a lot
of people start agencies and it takes
them one year to get the first client it
takes them two years to get a couple it
takes them three years to get 10K a
month like that's a pretty difficult
time frame
um I I don't know how open you are in
Revenue numbers but you're obviously
doing very well lead bird what would you
say is one of your differentiators
looking at other people that have spent
three years spinning reels or maybe just
getting to the point where they're like
a highly paid freelancer where you have
a legitimate agency if real market value
yeah so I think what the the
turn was for us because the sales was
hard for me but extremely hard you know
um what made it so much easier and this
is something that really kind of picked
up in the last
three months is just social proof
um and so you know working with clients
and getting the really good results
getting them on a interview with you
just like this speaking about their
results getting them to write a G2
review and then putting that on your
LinkedIn company page putting that on
your website you know just doing all
those kind of things just makes the
sales process so much easier because
like you know I have 15 video
testimonials on my site and I know you
guys crushed on that too right and I
have a 5 out of 5 stars on G2 and I have
this all documented everywhere and you
get on a sales call with me like and I
say hey I'm gonna deliver leads for you
on performance basis like who's gonna
say no to that offer you know like who's
gonna legitimately think that oh this
guy doesn't know what he's doing you
know
um and so it makes the sales process
ridiculously easy and like I wish I
learned that earlier on when I first
started the agency because we'd be much
bigger obviously so like you know if
you're watching this like biggest thing
I could advise you on is get those first
five videos is make them actually legit
don't just get your friend to shoot your
video testimonial make it legit with
legitimate companies and just watch your
agency grow from there on forwarding
I'm 100 with you on the social proof um
there was a there's a post that I
thought was interesting uh you know Alex
Becker right yeah yeah huge fan so he uh
he had posted something a couple days
ago where it's like in 2015 with
difficulty in online business because
knowing what to do because no
information was available because
information wasn't being monetized but
difficulty in 2023 is everybody has the
same information and it's great
information but there's so much
competition so it's it's everything's
easy to figure out now where back in the
day it was hard to figure out but there
was no competition so looking at
everybody who's starting business I mean
talking it's a lot of people doing lead
generation baby lead generation
um and it really you need to have that
trust to stand out because you're not
from your prospect size you're not
special unless you're special you need
to have you need to have that
credibility you need to have that
personal brand have those testimonials
because likely the person you're working
with is probably ripped off two or three
times before like I'm I don't I don't
know about you Nick both my clients most
of them I'm the second or third Legion
agency they've worked with is that the
same for you
yeah so you one of our biggest clients
actually they it's probably my favorite
video testimonial that I've ever gotten
but yeah we were the only Legion agency
that was able to deliver lease for them
because they've been burnt before and it
was it was it was pretty funny because
like
she was like the way she explained it
was like these other Legion agencies
like she gave them the lead list she
gave them the copy and literally nothing
came out of it you know and I was just
like how's that how's that possible you
know uh because she gave us the exact
same things and we crushed it you know
um and so I don't know I just thought
that was hilarious
yeah that is a pretty cool testimonial
well one question for you too is like
when I first started out in a legion
agency I started working with smaller
agencies who had my network is who I
could sell and I learned as time went on
but the bigger the company is the more
social proof they have same as when
you're selling and the more times
they've sold their offer you know like
for example we started with agencies
that had two clients we now have some
agencies but have up to ten thousand
like some really really big companies
I'm curious have you also found that
part of your growth has been working at
bigger companies it actually makes it
easier to deliver results
oh 100 I think everyone goes to that
learning curve right like when you first
start you kind of take whatever comes
your way and you can't really what's
that saying like Beggars can't be
choosers or whatever it is
um and so like you just kind of take on
anyone and that that's not always the
best thing to do and
like
I don't think people realize when it
comes to like outbound Legion like
having a brand and being like something
where you can Google and and find
relatively quickly plays such a huge
impact in terms of like results like you
know we still have like maybe one or two
very small clients and we we tell and we
like you know they don't get the best
results and we tell them like hey like
your landing page is literally just a
logo you know like what do you what do
you mean it's our fault you know and so
it's like just things like that uh uh
yeah but I definitely think that like
you know one of the reasons why we've
been able to grow recently is like we
worked with some really good brands and
huge companies that are like public
traded and you know obviously they paid
more and it's much easier to kind of get
responses when you know you're
hitting someone that's in their target
market because they know of them already
so it just I don't know it makes it much
easier that's a really good point one of
the common objections I hear to that
point is it's so hard to land big
clients which I personally have not
found to be significantly more difficult
have you found that or what is in your
process to land these big sometimes
publicly traded companies
so what I've noticed is you know
obviously the sales process takes longer
it's not hard to close them
um you kind of have to know how to
structure the deals though so like
obviously we do a paper lead model so
you know we're Performance Based you
know procurement departments they hate
variable expenses so kind of getting a
deal through the door when it's that
model does not always work like and it's
only going to delay things so like you
just got to know how to structure those
agreements
um you know you got to be prepared to
know that you know the sales cycle is
going to take a long time but if you're
just doing your follow-ups and just kind
of scheduling up those emails like
you're gonna get them eventually right
and then the other thing too is just
once again like kind of going back to
building your brand like you know they
they have to trust you because you're
going to be having a lot of a lot of
their information like for us like some
of our clients we have every single one
of their customers added to the DNC list
and it's like you know they're not gonna
just willingly give that to some random
vendor they found got a cool email from
and so they really do need to trust you
but in terms of sales it's it's it's
really just seeing if you fit into their
budget that they have planned out and so
that's that's really about it um and I
think the thing is like once you land
one of those accounts it makes it so
easy to go get those other accounts and
just kind of getting them on like a
trial phase with you is always worth it
like even if you're not making the most
money out of it like you'll be able to
actually grow those accounts like those
are those are clients that are going to
pay you you know 100 to 200k per year
per quarter
um and so like it's just worth it like
if you're taking that first initial
trial run with them at like you know
barely profitable it just makes sense
because like that's a company that you
can grow with versus like you know like
the the regular agency owner that just
spawned up yesterday like
like am I going to do performance for
them and possibly make some money like
I'm not going to take that chance like
it's not worth it I I am with you I also
don't like working at Facebook ads
agencies with no niche in a click
funnels website that has every templated
portion they ripped off of every popular
course
that's my favorite what are you talking
about I uh I I say stuff like that
sometimes I think maybe it comes off as
mean it's not mean because I was that
same person when I first started it's
just it's ambitious ignorance which I
can appreciate but there there is you
know like one thing I've noticed is all
our best clients have a phone number on
the website like having a phone number
on the website means you have to budget
to have someone to answer the phone yeah
yeah 100 that's a great point and
ironically we don't have a phone number
on the website so it's in our list but
you know uh we're actually one of a
small like I always say that I'm the
smallest of the companies I work with
because I I think I I probably am if
you're working at public companies I
would assume maybe the same too but it's
cool because you have to look at
insights because you get to work with
these guys that are where you want to be
and you can look and see all the things
behind the scenes so also working big
companies is great from educational
perspective
yeah no I agree I mean I like I think
the other thing too is like I mean we're
both young it's like not many people get
to and like I've never done a corporate
job or anything like that and so I've
never gotten to really peek into like
okay like seriously you know when you
first start out you're working with the
founder or like some owner or like a 10
person company but it's like now you're
working with like the director of like
marketing or something of that sort and
or like director of global Legion or
whatever demand and it's like they just
have a budget and I don't know it's just
like it's like a different feel like
working with them rather than working
like with like a founder and seeing how
like they communicate to their team and
it's it's kind of like a little bit more
political it's not like as
straightforward and like you know they
got to get clearance and they gotta ask
their boss about these things I don't
know it's just it's cool seeing that
because like I've never
seen that before in my my career
um and so it's a learning experience for
sure and how old are you Nick I actually
have no idea yeah so I'm actually 23 I'm
about to turn 24 and uh I think like 10
days or actually you know this weekend
uh four days so yeah happy birthday
you're a little bit older
well how old are you uh 23. but I turned
I turned 24 and uh next year
for everyone watching Michael's like 6
10. uh so it just doesn't look 23 at all
no it's funny because like I don't know
if this has been ever going to be
recurring Trend everyone I'm eating a BW
Legion in Space is really tall I've met
two guys in B2B Legion they're taller
than me all right we you're not gonna
find that with me I'm like 5 10. okay on
a good day
it's not too bad well cool all right so
um we talked a bit about leadbird we
talked about you know what companies
you're working with some of the
learnings you've had experience of a
company now I I'm curious
how do you compare running your your
software companies to your agency do you
you know what is the one one question I
wonder is like the agency you know you
might want to grow it for cash flow or
you might want to grow it to sell if the
software companies is the intent always
to build to sell or what what is like
the end goal when you're building these
companies because clearly you have a
have a lot of them too which I imagine
is a bit to manage
yeah so you know I
it's a hard one to answer because like
you know I've kind of gone around and
I'm kind of seeing like the mistakes
I've made and like how I kind of went
into it so first like I wouldn't have
jumped into so running like multiple
companies is is insanely hard like you
know if I was just focused on the agency
for the last three years and I wish I
did I'd be much further ahead than I am
right now right
um so that's the first thing um and I
wouldn't have and like if you don't come
from a technical background and you
don't have like the greatest development
team it's very hard to build a product
that and we're in tough spaces like
wearing spaces where we're fighting
Google's terms and services Link in
terms of services like they don't want
us to do email warm up and so it's like
you're never going to find documentation
and um like understand how to build that
product the right way it's like a lot of
your developers testing something seeing
if it works if it works scaling it
seeing if it's a scales if it doesn't
coming up with another solution it's
just like a lot of back and forth and
the other thing too is like I don't
think a lot of people realize that like
SAS has churn right and most Legion
products have a 10 churn rate right and
so if you're taking a product-led growth
method it's extremely hard to make it
like reasonable well first of all let's
make it like really worth your time
right because you're gonna have to jump
on a customer support call for some dude
that's paying you nine dollars a month
and like it's gonna churn out the next
month regardless and it's just like I
don't know like that that to me is just
a very tough model like I if I was to do
SAS again I would not do the plg method
I would do more of like an Enterprise
sales motion make them pay and collect
the LTD up up front like that just makes
more sense to me and that's kind of what
I want to Pivot some of these products
to I also want to shut down some of
these products because you know like
a great example was like Emmy like our
email was sending platform we had domain
rotation inbox rotation and all these
things way before like a lot of these
other products like instantly as early
then you know instantly smart read have
done a great job of making a stable
product that actually works and it's
incredible I use Smart beat now like I
literally don't even use the own email
sending platform but I built you know
and it's like things like that and I
don't want to have to compete with those
guys because they're gonna crush me
because they have a great development
team you know and so
that's kind of what I think about it
like I really like simple SAS products
quick lines is a great example it's very
simple very easy to use
um and there's not much of a back end
there like I haven't touched quick lines
and in six months it's done great in
terms of numbers
um and it just kind of is a cash flow
play for me in that sense I love to get
an exit eventually off of it and then
like scrubby and golden leads those are
two SAS products we just built recently
um I think those are gonna be really big
because it kind of does do things that
other products don't
um and they're also very simple backend
so it's not like you need a huge
development team and it's much easier to
control but like any inbox seat those
are those are pretty tough like it's
very hard building email setting
platforms um so yeah that's kind of like
a whole circle 360 of my my dealings
with SAS
but one thing I wonder if your SAS
companies is obviously you have an
advantage if you want to do cold email
for them you have a plug-and-play system
to then do code email for them but I
know you also have a nice personal brand
you've built up when it comes to getting
these users for your software companies
or for your agency what is the split
between personal brand and outbound
yeah so when it came so it's scrubby
actually this is actually funny so
um
eighty percent of our Revenue that we've
generated this year has come from six
customers and out of the six customers
one came from personal brand work
Network kind of thing and the other five
are comfortable emails and we have a ton
of other users you know majority of our
users do come from like you know content
personal brand kind of stuff they don't
they don't contribute to the the big
portion of our revenue and so that
that's kind of why I would rather take a
Enterprise sales motion and not get
people with my Twitter DMS asking me hey
uh why is this not working and it's like
you're just not using the product
correctly you know uh so I don't know
that's that's kind of how that's been
going but yeah we definitely run cool
EOS for all of our products
um you know it's obviously easy because
we have the agency and you know pretty
good plug-and-play system for it so why
not you know
I'm curious four four lead Birds
specifically do you mind sharing how
many people that you pulled email for
your own company per month
per month um so we're gonna rapidly
scale this because like uh
first time in the last three years where
I feel like fulfillment is like really
good and you know I have a pretty good
back-end team where like I'm really
confident in and so going into May we're
going to go full sales mode I've never
been able to do this and like we're kind
of prepping for it you know getting a
little CRM built out a little bit more
we've been running a really successful
golden campaign this month that's
probably done over 30 to 40 appointments
already and content's been picking up a
lot so that's also picking up a lot of
appointments so in my goal is to get a
new center to start doing cold calls get
a sales team in place get multiple
closers
um and and really crush it on our sales
side but in terms of so right now like
for the month of April we've probably
done
we probably added five to seven thousand
people into our campaign but going into
may I want to like 10x that not 10x
maybe 10x or like 30 to 50 000 uh 12
people added into a prospect for into a
campaign so uh I'm guessing if you're
doing that higher volume planning you
can't just be targeting agencies and a
lot of people need to we want to just um
how do you determine who you want to
Target is it by industry is it by
employee account
yeah so it varies I mean so we do
definitely still Target agencies you
know that's like kind of like
what's the the phrase like the the low
hanging fruit like you know you're going
to get appointments booked you know
you're going to close some of those
um it may not be the best clients but
like you know learning through
um I like to to hit a lot of people that
are in like people that have like roles
around demand gen
um those are those really good ones had
a growth those are really good titles
you just need to be able to build your
webos to be B2B obviously because you
know if you do head of growth you may
get a lot of b2c companies which is
obviously not going to work same people
demand gen
um and so yeah like it kind of depends
but we do have pretty good icps built
out and we have like a really
smart way of running like a like right
our campaign right now is like we're
able to scrape
our competitors
followers on their LinkedIn company page
and run old emails campaigns to them and
so that that prints for us right now um
and so we're gonna we're gonna replicate
that at scale and then we have like a
pretty good SEO play that's that's kind
of picking up right now too as well so
yeah I don't know I think going into May
June July it's like it's all about
customer acquisition which is like
something I enjoy obviously
and it's it's the fun part for sure
well sweet I um I think that leads to
one of the final questions here which
you know you're doing a lot of things
you're figuring out what you do and
don't like a software you're deciding to
scale the agency what what is the goal
here is the goal to sell all these
companies and go into real estate is it
to sell them and travel the world do you
just like building things like have you
put a lot of thought into where all this
is leading and how these companies are
going to take you there
yeah so I think the end goal is not
really like the end goal it's like I
want Libra to be a stable like a staple
name you know I don't want it like you
know when I think of like the biggest
guys in the lead Legion space I think of
science I think of belkins you know and
I want Libra to be up there with it
because I love sales I love Legion and
you know I really enjoy like working
with my team and I just I just wanted to
be one of the biggest up there and I'm
sure it looks like one of your goals as
well you know and it's something that
you know I just I mean that's kind of
like what motivates me day in day out
it's like you know I'm building some of
the like I like what I think is like
some of the greatest processes when it
comes to Legion you know across like all
companies and and you know it just it's
incredible to kind of see that kind of
come to play so yeah I don't know yeah
that's kind of like my goal just uh make
lever in a stable name for everything
and anything old Outreach Legion sales
uh take it from there
oh that's sweet well as a final sign off
Nick
um obviously I'll have lead bird and
I'll have some of your software
companies and probably your Twitter too
linked down below is there any other
tool or link you want to shout out
people connect with you or they can try
one of your products
yeah so you just type in Nick Abraham 12
YouTube Twitter or LinkedIn it'll pop up
to my profile and post some pretty good
content I think that's pretty good
content you guys can let me know
um and yeah that's really it and then
you'll probably see some of our products
on there scrubby golden leads and yeah
that'll probably take you to some of
those tools and you can test it out and
let us know if it's good uh give us some
feedback yeah that's that's really about
it
great well Nick thanks for coming on
thanks for having me
[Music]
foreign